jobwalkins.com 2011-11-24

# JOBWALKINS.COM

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services at http://www.Jobwalkins.com website and content. This document describes how  user information is collected, stored, used and, in specific instances, shared with Organizational users. By accepting this Privacy Policy , you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy.

Information You Will Be Asked To Provide When Using the website  
If you choose to register with us in order to take advantage of the web services, you will be asked to provide  name, email address. **_

Purpose and Use of Your Personal Information

_**  
We may use your personal information To provide you with information about other products and services ,alerts. ** _

Cookies

_**  
The log-in area on the we require that your browser accept cookies. A cookie is  
a small amount of information that is sent from a web server to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

Contacting Us  
If you wish to review or correct your information as set forth in the website ,inform us how you wish your information to be used, please contact one of our Administrators. You may contact our Administrators by mail, e-mail or telephone.
